who needs raw fish when you can enjoy
these vegan avocado sushi rolls place a
nori sheet rough side up onto a bamboo
mat and then add one cup of sushi rice
spread this out to all the edges wet
your fingers in order to make spreading
it out even easier make sure you leave
just a little bit of room on the edge
there slice up some avocados and place
them slightly off center towards you
along with some julienned carrots and
cucumbers and then sprinkle on just a
little bit of salt starting from the end
closest to you start rolling up your
sushi roll and make sure that you make
it nice and tight and you remember that
little bit of nori we left at the end
you want to wet your fingers and slide
this across this will help seal the roll
dip a knife into some water to make
cutting the sushi an absolute breeze oh
yeah and don't forget to drizzle on a
little bit of sriracha mayo and sprinkle
with some sesame seeds hope you enjoy
guys